{
  "LevelId": 17,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 166,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "GALGANGALS",
      "question": "Aromatic rhizomes used in cooking"
    },
    {
      "id": 167,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "ANTIDOTES",
      "question": "Substances used to counteract poisons"
    },
    {
      "id": 168,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "FESTIVALS",
      "question": "Celebratory events or occasions"
    },
    {
      "id": 169,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BASEMENTS",
      "question": "Subterranean or underground living spaces"
    },
    {
      "id": 170,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BLOODROOT",
      "question": "Plants with red sap used historically for dye"
    },
    {
      "id": 171,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BALCONIES",
      "question": "Outdoor elevated platforms attached to buildings"
    },
    {
      "id": 172,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BIRTHMARK",
      "question": "Permanent skin discoloration present at birth"
    },
    {
      "id": 173,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BLUEJEANS",
      "question": "Casual pants made of denim fabric"
    },
    {
      "id": 174,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "AFTERNOON",
      "question": "The time between noon and evening"
    },
    {
      "id": 175,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "COSMETICS",
      "question": "Products used for enhancing beauty or appearance"
    },
    {
      "id": 176,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "GOVERNMENT",
      "question": "System or organization for controlling and managing a community or country"
    }
  ]
}